<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SmsCodeHelper</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="introduce">SmsCodeHelper, is a new open source of light App.\n\nIt can automatically emerge verification code when your phone  receives a text message contains a  verification code. And automatically copy the code to the user\'s clipboard. When the user receives the message verification code, just long press the EditText to paste the verification code.\n\nIn addition, it can also allow users to bulk delete unwanted SMS verification code; It can also help users Backward inference out what the business is bound (for a new phone number, it is useful).\n\nIt is very light, but also adhering to the usual good design and user-friendly, since it does not start at leisure, will not take up any memory (unbelievers or concern, welcome to view the source code) .\n\nOpen source address: https: //github.com/drakeet/SmsCodeHelper\n\nWe open source, good design, not indiscriminately use rights. Just hope if you like it, you can share with your friends, because good things need to share with others in order to let it grow, every share is our power, thanks!</string>
    <string name="share">Share to Friends (thank you)</string>
    <string name="guess">Backward inference of bundled services</string>
    <string name="share_text">Found a very beautiful and easy to use app: SmsCodeHelper (verification code helper), light, open source, it can automatically copy the code to the user\'s clipboard, when the user receives the message verification code.  Material Design and open source: http://fir.im/codehelper (or Google Play: SmsCodeHelper)</string>
    <string name="str_no_bussiness">Temporarily did not find any business is bound.</string>
    <string name="str_doing_hint">Being recognized, please wait.</string>
    <string name="str_check_bussiness_hint">Backward inference of bundled services</string>
    <string name="str_clear_messages_hint">All messages contain verification code will be deleted, but we will still save you records (for Backward inference). Please double-check and confirm the operation!</string>
    <string name="str_version_morethan_five">Android 5.0+ does not support emptied verification code text message temporarily.</string>
    <string name="tip">Verification code: %s, and has been copied to the clipboard, press your input box to paste the code.</string>
    <string name="notify_msg">Current verification code:%s (Click to copy)</string>
    <string name="app_name_with_introduce">SmsCodeHelper - Convenient for Verification code</string>
    <string name="developers">Developers</string>
    <string name="developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="developer_and_designer"><![CDATA[Developer & Designer]]></string>
    <string name="open_source_lis">Open source licenses</string>
    <string name="introduce_and_help">Introduction and help</string>
</resources>
